Full force, frontal assault!
全軍突擊
Kill all of these inferior races!
把那群劣等種族屠殺殆盡
You asked me to surrender.
妳想叫我投降?
I'll go ahead and ask you the same exact thing.
我把這句話原封不動還給妳
You have no choice but to bow down
面對五千人的樂園部隊
before a 5,000 man strong Paradise Corps.
你們也只能乖乖屈服
How silly.
真是愚蠢
What?
什麼
An army built on violence and fear is
靠暴力與恐懼打造的軍隊
a dime a dozen.
充其量只是烏合之眾
No, there's no point in saying it.
不 說這些也沒用
Anyway, I came here
總之朕會來這裡
to see your final moments.
是為了見證你的死期
What a joke.
還在說笑
Sounds like the howling of a loser to me.
聽起來就像輸家打死不認輸
To the people of the world, good afternoon!
全世界的觀眾 大家好
This is Melka Tiano of the Six Nations Newspaper!
我是六國新聞的梅露可．堤亞
This is my first time attempting something like this
第一次嘗試這種做法 有點緊張
and I am nervous, but I have something to share with you!
但是有件事必須讓大家知道
What I'm calling 〝The Darkness of Gera-Alka〞
這個真相堪稱 蓋拉．阿爾卡的黑暗面
will be easier to explain by showing you rather than reporting.
比起用講的
Please look at all of these holding cells!
各位請看 如此大量的牢獄
We are underneath Gera-Alka's Dream Paradise.
這裡是蓋拉．阿爾卡 夢想樂園的地底
It isn't only supporters of the Alka royalty who are held here!
裡面關的不僅是 阿爾卡王室的支持者
Various races from other countries are also unjustly held
還有他國各種族被違法抓來
and subjected to inhuman experimentation!
被迫進行非人道的人體實驗
Ms. Melka let's go home! We're going to get ourselves killed!
梅露可小姐 我們回去吧
It doesn't matter if we're killed!
被殺掉也無所謂
A soldier must die on the battlefield!
死在戰場上才是我的本願
Can you please remember you are a journalist, not a warrior?
妳的思維不是記者而是戰士吧 不能改掉嗎
This is clearly an act against humanity.
這顯然是違反人道的行為
President Madhart, who oversaw these atrocities,
這個殘暴惡行的主謀 馬特哈德總統
is planning to attack Fort Fall with an army of 5,000!
甚至出動了五千人大軍
Can the world continue to allow evil to rule?
你們容許世界繼續遭到惡徒支配嗎
Of course it can't!
絕對不容許
So this is Nelia's Rekkaku Liberation?
這就是納莉亞的烈核解放
Yes!
沒錯
Sword Flower of Extermination!
"盡劉之劍花"
My sword will cut down all that is evil!
我的劍將斬斷一切之惡
Everyone, we've come to save you.
各位 我來救你們了
Hurry and go!
快走吧
Stand with me to change Alka!
奮起改變阿爾卡吧
At last, Lady Nelia has taken a stand!
納莉亞大人終於挺身而出了
This'll be the end of Madhart!
馬特哈德完蛋了
No matter what
不論如何
I am going to change Alka!
我都會改變阿爾卡
Lady Nelia, there's no point in doing this.
納莉亞大人…
Why?
為什麽
Gertrude!
凱特蘿
Lady Nelia...
納莉亞大人…
You are my servant!
妳是我的僕從
It's time I punished the maid who betrayed her master!
竟敢反抗主人 像妳這種女僕必須接受懲罰
You're wrong!
不是的
This was all done for you Lady Nelia!
我的所作所為都是為了您好
Despite being my servant...
明明只是僕從
You dare to
不准反抗我
What did you want me to do?
妳到底想要我怎麼做
You cannot defeat Madhart.
不能打倒馬特哈德
That man is a hero in a real bad way.
雖然是負面的意思
That's why...
所以…
I didn't want you to be hurt
我不希望您受到更多傷害
You are Rainsworth's little sister right?
妳是雷因史瓦斯的妹妹吧
I thought you didn't care about me at all.
難道妳不是把我當不重要的存在嗎
You're wrong.
絕對不是
I have been abused by my brother.
我…一直深受哥哥虐待
He said if you're not strong, you're not worthy of living.
他常說不夠強就沒有活下去的價值
But you always cared for me Lady Nelia.
但是…
You always worried about me when I got hurt.
我受傷了 您會為我擔心
You even celebrated my birthday with me.
還會幫我慶祝生日
That's why I wanted you to forget all the hard times
所以…
and live your life in peace.
過上和平的生活才對
My brother is a scumbag, but at least
雖然哥哥是個人渣
he takes care of the things that are 〝his.〞
但他對於自己的"所有物" 都會格外珍惜
I don't need peace that comes with living as someone's pet.
我不需要在別人豢養下獲得和平
I'm sorry.
對不起
Thank you for everything up to now.
至今為止謝謝您的關照
Please just forget about me.
請您忘了我吧
You were being rebellious.
妳只是進入反抗期罷了
I don't get all upset when one of my servants
只是被一名僕人反咬一小口
bites the hand that feeds.
我才不會因為這種小事發火
Just tell me if there's something upsetting you.
但如果妳有什麼不滿 要跟我說
It's not good to keep it bottled up.
只有單方面滿足的人際關係不太好
Lady Nelia...
納莉亞大人…
Ms. Komari, Ms. Cunningham...
可瑪莉小姐 克寧格姆小姐
Carla?
迦流羅
What?
幹嘛 我正要去追捕雷因史瓦斯
Our enemy seems to have a force of 5,000.
聽說對方是五千人大軍
There's no way for you to win by yourself, Ms. Cunningham.
妳一個人去應戰也沒有勝算
I'll fight even if there isn't a chance.
沒有勝算也要戰鬥
That's my role to play.
這就是我的使命
If you go on a suicide mission, you'll just die in vain.
單槍匹馬衝去 只是去白白送死
Can we not first think of a strategy?
要不要先想好作戰
But I thought you were
但是…
the Five Sword Emperor who destroys the universe.
妳不是強到能破壞宇宙的五劍帝嗎
Um, that's right but
是沒錯
let's plan a strategy to be on the safe side.
但為了確保萬無一失 還是來擬訂作戰計劃吧
I don't understand you.
剛才為什麼要停頓
Anyway, you do have a point.
不過妳說的有道理
The enemy is too powerful for our forces.
以我方的戰力來看
We've exposed their evil, but it'll be futile if we are defeated by their might.
雖然已經揭發了惡行
To counter them,
為了對抗敵軍
the people of the world must all join hands and stand together.
全世界的人民必須攜手共戰
Komari, come here a second.
可瑪莉 可以借一步說話嗎
-What-- -Ms. Nelia!
怎…怎麼了
We can't fully trust you yet.
我還沒辦法相信妳
Do not approach Ms. Komari!
請不要靠近可瑪莉小姐
No need to have your guard up.
不必處處提防
Komari and I have already shared blood.
因為我跟可瑪莉 是共享血液的關係了
It can't be!
難道說
You fed Lady Komari your blood?
您逼可瑪莉大小姐喝下您的血
No, Komari actually fed me her blood.
不 是可瑪莉讓我喝了她的血
What are you doing?
妳…妳在做什麼
It's to thank you.
這是回禮 讓妳喝我的血
Blood?
血
No, wait! You don't need to do that!
等一下 不需要這麼做
I've received your blood
妳都把血分給我了
so if you won't suck my blood I'll feel sad.
如果不喝我的血 我會很傷心
The thought is enough, really.
妳…妳的好意我心領了
I'll drink some tomato juice instead.
我會喝番茄汁代替的
I won't have it.
那怎麼行
Komari.
可瑪莉 妳擁有極為驚人的力量
Even if you say so...
就算妳那麼說…
My teacher was your mother.
我的老師是妳的媽媽
That makes us sisters of a sort.
換句話說 我們就像是姐妹
Could you just try to trust what your big sister is telling you?
能不能試著相信姐姐說的話?
But...
可是…
I want to change the world with you.
我想跟妳一起改變這個世界
I feel like now we will be able to.
我覺得我們現在一定辦得到
I cannot forgive those who cause other's pain.
絕不原諒傷害大家的人
The world isn't just for Madhart.
這個世界不是專屬於馬特哈德一人
It's for everyone!
而是屬於大家的
That's right.
沒錯
I don't know what I can do about it.
雖然我不曉得自己能做些什麼
But I want to fight by your side!
但我想要跟妳並肩作戰
What is that?
那是什麼
Look at that, people of the world!
全世界的觀眾請看
At last Terakomari Gandesblood is giving us her all!
黛拉可瑪莉．崗德森布萊德閣下 終於拿出了真本事
She is going to save the world!
這樣世界就能得救了
Komari, Komari!
可瑪莉…
Please share your thoughts!
請發表一下現在的心情
I will destroy Gera-Alka!
我要毀了蓋拉．阿爾卡
At least we bought time
至少成功爭取時間讓市民逃脫了…
I can't believe it.
真是的
I can't face Lady Karen looking like this.
實在沒臉回去見卡蕾大人
Millicent Blueknight?
米莉桑德．布魯奈特
You poor things.
真可憐
I'll kill them for you.
我就殺了你們吧
With a low level spell like that?
憑那種初級魔法…
Now go forth 5th Corps.
好了 去吧 第五部隊
Go take the burden from them.
給他們一個痛快
I see.
原來如此
You've been given the 5th Corps to take over?
第五部隊由妳接手了
Yes, and it's a pain in the ass.
真是麻煩事上身
Who are you?
妳這傢伙是誰
They told me I had to atone for my sins by earning my keep.
有人叫我立功贖罪 不過…
But it looks like she's decided to join the fight.
到頭來那傢伙還是會殺出來
Looks like I won't get any credit.
我根本沒有立功的機會
What are you saying? Who is 〝she?〞
妳在說什麼
A little brat who I hate.
就是我最討厭的小妞
I could kill you if you want.
我大可殺了你
But I guess it would be more effective to let her do it.
但還是留給那傢伙動手 效果會更好吧
I'll let you take over for the day
今天就先讓給妳吧
Terakomari!
黛拉可瑪莉
Rainsworth!
雷因史瓦斯
It's time to pay the piper!
遭報應的時刻到了
Don't be ridiculous!
開什麼玩笑
You should just obey my commands!
妳只要服從我就好了
If you do, I promise you eternal happiness!
我保證會讓妳永遠幸福
Yeah, no thanks.
我拒絕
I'm happy enough fighting alongside Komari.
我只要跟可瑪莉 並肩作戰就夠幸福了
Same for you too, right Komari?
對吧 可瑪莉妳也這麼覺得吧
Don't you dare look at me
不准用那種眼神
Ludicrous...
不可能
This is ludicrous!
這不可能
To all across the world who now hold a grudge against Gera-Alka!
對蓋拉．阿爾卡 懷恨在心的全世界人民
Now is the time to stand up! I am now taking a stand!
現在正是挺身對抗的時候
Change back to Alka!
阿爾卡需要變革
Now's the time to take a stand!
現在正是奮起之時
Terakomari Gandesblood...
黛拉可瑪莉．崗德森布萊德…
You're sensing it too, aren't you?
你應該也察覺到了吧
That girl
她是能夠引領人心的吸血鬼
Her Excellency is truly the most powerful vampire meant to rule this world.
閣下才是有資格統治世界的 最強吸血鬼
I have a message from Lord Oomikami.
大神大人聯絡
He wants us to knock out the Paradise Corps.
叫我們把樂園部隊打得稀巴爛
Our mission is still ongoing?
任務還要繼續啊
Fair enough. Honored brother Kakumei
好吧
just might be watching my battle somewhere out there.
看著我戰鬥的模樣
What?
什麼
The opportunists at Immortal Haven
本來在觀望情勢的夭仙鄉
have declared war on Gera-Alka?
正式向蓋拉．阿爾卡宣戰了
So then Gera-Alka is my only enemy?
這表示只有蓋拉．阿爾卡是敵人
I like the simplicity!
非常單純 這不是挺好的嗎
Come, my dear soldiers!
去吧 親愛的士兵們
Go forth and leave our enemies in shreds!
把敵人們大卸八塊 射成蜂窩吧
Nelia!
納莉亞
You are way out of line!
妳誤入歧途了
This won't help you at all!
做這種事 對妳沒有任何幫助
Come back by my side!
回到我身邊吧
I've come back right now.
我這不就回來了嗎
To defeat you that is!
回來擊敗你
What is this?
這到底是怎麼搞的
Wait Komari!
等等 可瑪莉
He's mine to put an end to.
這傢伙交給我解決
You paltry Ji-Lius! Seize Nelia!
翦劉們
Get out of my way!
可惡 不要妨礙我
Rekkaku Liberation, Swift Varja!
烈核解放
Die!
去死
Terakomari Gandesblood!
黛拉可瑪莉．崗德森布萊德
That'll be as good as confetti
那種攻擊碰上金剛不壞之身
facing the body of Varja!
就跟紛飛的紙片沒兩樣
This can't be...
騙人的吧
It is.
這不是在騙人
You inferior species dare to
區區劣等種族 竟敢這麼囂張
Give up.
死心吧
You are wrong.
你是錯的
I'm never wrong!
我怎麼可能是錯的
Gera-Alka will be destroyed.
蓋拉．阿爾卡將會毀滅
Nelia...
納莉亞…
My hometown was sold to another country
都是提倡和平主義的阿爾卡王
by King Alka, who always advocated for pacifism.
害我的故鄉被賣給了他國
I struggled to endure the discrimination
我一邊保護年幼的妹妹
while protecting my young sister.
一邊拼命忍受所有的歧視
As I endured it, I burned with a desire for revenge.
咬緊牙關忍耐 同時燃起復仇心
A desire for revenge against the other races
發誓向虐待我們的其他種族
who bullied us and against the slow-witted King Alka.
以及膽小的阿爾卡王復仇
In order to take revenge, I needed to become stronger.
為了如願復仇 不得不變強
I needed strength to get everything I lost back.
想要奪回一切 就需要力量
You've really got guts.
你還挺有骨氣的嘛
You could be a good pawn to help me conquer the world.
或許會是幫忙征服世界的優秀手下
I always...
我…我對妳…
In your own way
或許你是以你的方式
you may have been trying to do your best for Alka and the Ji-Liu.
為了阿爾卡和翦劉而努力
But you were working in the wrong direction.
但是你努力的方向錯了
Nelia, move aside.
納莉亞 讓開
Reflect on your mistakes.
好好反省吧
Looks like the fight's over.
勝負已定
It's not fair!
太…太卑鄙了
How could I fight against such power?
面對那種力量 是要如何抵抗
There's no strategy or plan that would work!
叫人怎麼想得出像樣的對策
With the power of Terakomari Gandesblood
心想只要有黛拉可瑪莉． 崗德森布萊德的力量
you knew the Ji-Liu didn't stand a chance!
翦劉根本不是對手
So Madhart,
聽朕說 馬特哈德
I am aiming to conquer the world.
朕的目標是征服世界
However, I don't intend to
但並非像你一樣 靠武力獨占世界
I will make an ideal world where people help one another.
而是要打造一個
That is the goal of the Mulnite Empire.
這就是姆爾納特帝國的目的
How frivolous. That's impossible!
無聊透頂
People are animals that only think of themselves!
人類這種生物只會想到自己
Komari is different.
可瑪莉不一樣
Guiding people's hearts in the right direction is
引領人心走上正途
that girl's role.
就是她的使命
You can't be serious!
妳是在開玩笑吧
In fact, that 〝Princess Getto〞 was saved by Komari.
實際上那位"月桃姬" 已經被可瑪莉拯救
People inspired by Komari
那些被可瑪莉感化的人
forget the foolish idea of 〝subjugating others with force.''
會逐漸遺忘"靠蠻力征服別人" 這種愚蠢的觀念
If we can increase those kinds of people
只要這樣的人越來越多
I suspect we'll realize my nation's ideal world.
肯定就能達成我國的理想
All with just a simple girl?
只不過是個小女孩
It's about time the curtains close.
差不多該落幕了
T-This is--
怎麼可能有這種事
Happening right now! Give it up!
就是有
After the Great War of the Six Nations,
在六國大戰終結後
with the disappearance of President Madhart,
馬特哈德總統似乎下落不明
the Republic of Gera-Alka
因此蓋拉．阿爾卡共和國
will be holding a new presidential election!
即將舉辦新任總統大選
What happened?
怎麼了嗎
Talk to big sis why don't ya?
說給大姐姐聽吧
Lord Ohii is angry with me.
我被公主大人臭罵了一頓
Did you know, Amatsu?
天津你知道嗎
The Inverted Moon has no mercy for those who fail.
逆月對於失敗者可是毫不留情喔
It'll be your head! Your head!
要被斬首啦 斬首
No, our strategy was a big success.
不 這次的作戰非常成功
Hey, wait! Don't eat my Taiyaki.
等等 不要偷吃我的鯛魚燒
Our strategy succeeded?
你說作戰非常成功?
Our goal was to destroy Gera-Alka.
我們的目的是摧毀蓋拉．阿爾卡
First time I'm hearing about it...
這我還是第一次聽說
Lord Ohii could not forgive Madhart.
公主大人無法原諒馬特哈德
They were conducting cruel human experiments
因為他們利用魔核的無限再生能力
using the magic core's ability to infinitely regenerate.
進行非人道的人體實驗
These vicious acts are only possible because the cores exist.
都是因為有魔核那種東西
Lord Ohii would be angry at that.
怪不得公主大人會生氣
So we seduced Madhart with the Sacred Articles
所以我們才以神具為誘餌 推了馬特哈德一把
and led him into a war he couldn't win.
唆使他打了一場沒有勝算的戰爭
Then why is Lord Ohii angry with you?
那公主大人為什麼要罵你
I was told to take care of my family.
她叫我好好珍惜家人
It's been a while since I've come here.
好久沒來這裡了
Lady Nelia, I'm sorry for being late.
納莉亞大人 對不起我來晚了
You are late...
太慢了吧 明明是妳叫我來的…
Father?
爸爸
Nelia!
納莉亞
Father! You're okay!
爸爸 原來你平安無事
I'm sorry I couldn't save you.
對不起我沒能去救你
No, you did an amazing job.
不 妳已經相當努力了
You are a much better Ji-Liu than I ever was.
妳是比我更加優秀的翦劉
Father!
爸爸…
DIE!
去死啦
You Gera-Alka rust buckets!
這群蓋拉．阿爾卡的鐵鏽
I'm going to be the one who gets the free head pat
請閣下摸摸頭的特權是我的
Hey you! That one was mine!
喂 混蛋
You're full of it!
別說笑了
I found him first!
是我先發現的
I can't abide a thief!
竟敢搶走 不可原諒 去死
Rejoice Lady Komari.
請您高興點 可瑪莉大小姐
-Things are going south for the enemy. -How could I rejoice at this?
敵人都被嚇跑了
How did it get like this?
為什麼會變成這樣
Nelia and I were supposed to have been friends.
還以為我跟納莉亞萌生了 友情般的情誼
I assume she wants to defeat Lady Komari to grow her popularity
大概是為了接下來的總統大選拉票
in order to collect votes in the upcoming presidential election?
想打倒您 趁機打響名號吧
I've finally gotten to you.
終於到了
Komari...
可瑪莉
Become my servant!
來當我的僕從吧
I'd never do that!
誰要啊
If you want to resist, go for it.
妳想抵抗的話就抵抗吧
But you are destined to walk beside me.
反正妳注定要跟我一起走下去
We both aim to create world peace.
我們是目標打造世界和平的同志
If we combine our power nobody in the world stands a chance!
只要兩人同心協力
Drinking Lady Komari's blood seems to have gotten to your head.
您只不過是喝了可瑪莉大小姐的血
I envy you.
羨慕死了
I'm going to twist your whole body like a rag
真想把她的身體像抹布一樣擰乾
to squeeze Lady Komari's blood out of you.
把可瑪莉大小姐的血榨出來
Stop being scary Vill!
這樣很恐怖耶 薇兒
Ms. Villhaze is right!
薇兒海絲小姐說得好
If I kill her
只要殺掉她
there'll be nobody in the world who has tasted Lady Komari's blood!
喝過可瑪莉小姐的血的人
Now you're saying scary things Sakuna!
妳也不要脫口而出那麼恐怖的發言
Komari!
可瑪莉
Ms. Komari!
可瑪莉小姐
Lady Komari!
可瑪莉大小姐
I knew it.
我還是…
I'd rather be a shut-in.
《家裡蹲吸血姬的鬱悶》 想回去當家裡蹲